https://www.juddlawfirm.com/privacy-policy-disclaimer/

Skip navigation.
Call Us Today for a Free Consultation(202) 483-6070   HomeFirmHow We WorkKevin D. JuddKevin D. Judd concentrates his law practice on consumer bankruptcy laws, which includes chapter 7 bankruptcy and chapter 13 bankruptcy.
Read MoreBankruptcyBankruptcyOverviewChapter 13BankruptcyChapter 7BankruptcyHomeForeclosuresManagingConsumer DebtBankruptcyMeans TestSolutions forStudent Loan DebtFrequently AskedQuestionsFAQFrequently Asked Questions
What are Different Types of Bankruptcy?
Where Should a Bankruptcy Case be Filed?
Who is Eligible to File a Chapter 7 Bankruptcy and Maintain a Chapter 7 Case?
What are the Typical Steps to Filing a Chapter 7 Bankruptcy Case and Obtaining a Discharge?
What are the Typical Steps to Filing a Chapter 13 Bankruptcy and Completing a Chapter 13 Case?
Bankruptcy NewslettersWhat to Expect When Filing for BankruptcyThe decision to file for bankruptcy is not an easy one. The stigma, the damage to your credit and ...Read MoreFeesWarningBankruptcy BlogWhy Washington D.C. is Struggling With Company ForeclosuresWashington D.C. is a busy and thriving city with many families and busy workers. Foreclosures can happen in housing areas and neighborhoods that are rapidly growing and changing. The process of a residential foreclosure, however, is pretty different than the process for ...Read MoreStudent Loan Repayment Options Before BankruptcyValuing your education is incredibly important, and for many Americans, going to college and getting a degree is a life goal and major milestone. However, with going to college means having to take out student loans. Sometimes, the amount of student loans is enormous, and ...Read MoreWhat are some bankruptcy exemptions?One of the biggest fears associated with filing for bankruptcy is the fear of loss. While one is facing severe financial struggle, it can be scary to realize that there’s a chance you’ll be losing most of your property. Filing bankruptcy under Chapter 7 means that ...Read MoreQuestionnaireContact Us
Law Firm of Kevin D. Judd
601 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW
Suite 900-South Building
Washington, DC 20004
Phone: (202) 483-6070
Click Here for Directions
Let Us Review Your CaseName *FirstLastEmail *Phone *Message *Checkboxes *I have read and understand the Privacy Policy.NameSubmit
Search for:
Let Us Review Your CaseName *FirstLastEmail *Phone *Message *Checkboxes *I have read and understand the Privacy Policy.PhoneSubmitHome » Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy for Bankruptcy Information Provided by Our Bankruptcy AttorneyLocated Near the Navy Memorial/Metro Station and Serving Clients in Washington DC and Throughout MarylandThis privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing How this information is transferred to a third party: We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. How is this information used by the company: We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, (e.g. to process your claim). Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Your Access to and Control Over Information Opt out statement& modify/delete statement:You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone or you can e-mail us through our website’s home page.Free initial phone consultation for bankruptcy information.
Free Case EvaluationPrivacy PolicyContact UsSitemap
Law Firm of Kevin D. Judd P.L.L.C.
601 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW
Suite 900-South Building
Washington, DC 20004
(202) 483-6070
Click here for directions
Connect with us:
Call Now (202) 483-6070We are a debt relief agency. We help people file for bankruptcy relief under the Bankruptcy Code.This Website is designed for general information only. The information present on this website should not be construed to be formal legal advice, nor the formation of a lawyer-client relationship.© 2007–2020 Law Firm of Kevin D. Judd, P.L.L.C.
Law Firm Marketing provided by
& Attorneys Online, Inc.
